jinises.com 2017-05-07

# Jinises Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order or register to the site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1\. To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

2\. To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

The only cookie that is ever stored is when you click the "keep me logged in" box on the log in page. We do not use cookies for your transactions. If you cancel while creating the ad or leave create or edit ad pages before finalizing the transaction, your information regarding that transaction will be removed from our database.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on 11/7/2015

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

3898 Bufflehead dr.   
Columbus, Ohio 43230  
United States of America  
Jinises@jinises.com  
614-316-8402
